<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CT-Travel</string>
    <string name="city">city</string>
    <string name="locations">locations</string>

    <string name="cn1">France </string>
    <string name="cn2">Spain</string>
    <string name="cn3">Japan</string>
    <string name="cn4">United Arab Emirates</string>
    <string name="cn5">United States of America</string>


    <string name="entertainment">Entertainment</string>
    <string name="shopping">Shopping Location</string>
    <string name="history">Historical Location</string>
    <string name="hotel">Resorts and Hotels</string>
    <string name="nature">Nature and Wildlife</string>

    <string name="cd1">Paris: a city of romance and elegance... Immerse yourself in the artistic spirit that inspires countless creatives, indulge in delectable French cuisine at charming cafés, and savor the beauty of its historic architecture. With its vibrant street life, world-class museums, and enchanting atmosphere,</string>
    <string name="cd2">Barcelona: a lively city bursting with creativity and passion... Embrace the vibrant Catalan culture, savor the rich flavors of Mediterranean cuisine, and soak in the artistic spirit that fills the streets. With its lively festivals, colorful architecture, and friendly locals, Barcelona offers an enchanting experience.</string>
    <string name="cd3">Tokyo: a mesmerizing tapestry of history and innovation... Immerse yourself in the harmonious blend of ancient traditions and cutting-edge technology, savoring authentic Japanese cuisine and experiencing the lively atmosphere of bustling streets. With its unique fashion, art, and culture.</string>
    <string name="cd4">Dubai: a captivating blend of tradition and modernity... Experience the vibrant fusion of cultures, indulge in exquisite culinary delights, and revel in the luxurious lifestyle that defines this dynamic city. From bustling markets to upscale boutiques, every corner offers a unique taste of Dubais charm,</string>
    <string name="cd5">Kalebsgrad, Silopolov Empire</string>

    <string name="c1l1">A majestic symbol of French history, the Arc de Triomphe stands proudly at the western end of the Champs-Élysées in Paris. This monumental arch was commissioned by Napoleon Bonaparte in 1806 to honor the victories of the French army. Visitors can climb to the top for panoramic views of the city and witness the intricate carvings and inscriptions that commemorate significant battles and military leaders. The Tomb of the Unknown Soldier, located beneath the arch, is marked by an eternal flame that burns in memory of those who died in World War I. The Arc de Triomphe is not just a monument, but a powerful reminder of Frances enduring spirit and heritage.</string>
    <string name="c1l2">The Paris Catacombs. A veritable labyrinth in the heart of underground Paris, the Catacombs were installed in the tunnels of former quarries. Twenty meters underground in a maze of galleries, visitors will discover an extensive network of ossuaries(room used to store the bones of the dead) holding the remains of over six million people, offering a fascinating and eerie glimpse into historical past of France. </string>
    <string name="c1l3">An object of discord, desire, and fascination, the Eiffel Tower never fails to impress. Like all towers, it allows us to see and to be seen, with a spectacular ascent, a unique panoramic view of Paris, and a glittering beacon in the skies of the Capital. As night falls, the tower transforms into a mesmerizing light show, enchanting both visitors and locals alike.</string>
    <string name="c1l4">Louvre, national museum and art gallery of France, housed in part of a large palace in Paris that was built on the right-bank site of the 12th-century fortress of Philip Augustus. It is the world’s most-visited art museum, with a collection that spans work from ancient civilizations to the mid-19th century. Home to masterpieces such as the Mona Lisa and the Venus de Milo, the Louvre offers an unparalleled journey through art history and cultural heritage.</string>
    <string name="c1l5">The Seine River is among the most beautiful places to see in Paris for an unforgettable and fulfilling experience. The Seine, ancient Sequana, is the second largest river in France. The river flows below the Eiffel Tower and is surrounded by spectacular views of huge skyscapes, century-old trees, and monumental places. A cruise along the Seine offers a unique perspective of the iconic architecture of paris and historic sites, making it a must-see for any visitor.</string>
    <string name="c1l6">Champs-Élysées is a popular commercial street in Paris. Also called the Avenue des Champs-Élysées, its home to a variety of luxury shopping establishments, cafes, and theaters. Stretching from the Arc de Triomphe to the Place de la Concorde, this iconic avenue is renowned for its grandiosity and vibrant atmosphere, making it a must-visit destination for both tourists and locals. During the holiday season, the avenue is beautifully illuminated, adding to its charm and appeal.</string>

    <string name="c2l1">An object of awe, inspiration, and architectural brilliance, the Basílica de la Sagrada Família never fails to captivate. Like all great monuments, it allows us to witness and appreciate exceptional artistry, with its intricate facades and towering spires offering a unique view of Barcelonian skyline. As one of Antoni Gaudí masterpieces, the basilica stands as a testament to his innovative vision and remains an enduring symbol of Catalan culture and creativity. Each visit reveals new details and evokes a profound sense of wonder and reverence.</string>
    <string name="c2l2">An enchanting blend of nature and architecture, Park Guell is a must-see destination in Barcelona. Designed by the renowned architect Antoni Gaudi, the park features a whimsical array of colorful mosaics, undulating forms, and organic shapes that seamlessly integrate with the surrounding landscape. As you wander through its pathways, you will encounter beautifully sculpted terraces, vibrant tile work, and panoramic views of the city. Park Guell is not only a testament to Gaudis genius but also a vibrant oasis that offers a unique and magical experience for visitors of all ages.</string>
    <string name="c2l3">A treasure trove of art and history, the Picasso Museum in Barcelona is an essential destination for art lovers. Housed in five adjoining medieval palaces in the La Ribera neighborhood, the museum boasts one of the most extensive collections of artworks by the renowned artist Pablo Picasso. The collection spans Picassos early years, offering a deep dive into his formative periods and showcasing his evolution as an artist. As you explore the museum, you will encounter masterpieces that reflect his versatility and genius, making it a captivating experience for visitors.</string>
    <string name="c2l4">A pilgrimage site for football enthusiasts, Camp Nou is the iconic home stadium of FC Barcelona. Located in the heart of the city, this colossal stadium is one of the largest in Europe, with a seating capacity of nearly 100,000. Visitors can immerse themselves in the rich history of the club through the Camp Nou Experience, which includes a tour of the stadium, the press room, the changing rooms, and the pitch. The museum showcases a vast collection of trophies, memorabilia, and interactive exhibits that celebrate the clubs glorious legacy. </string>
    <string name="c2l5">A journey through time, the Gothic Quarter is the historic heart of Barcelona. This enchanting neighborhood is characterized by its narrow medieval streets, ancient buildings, and stunning Gothic architecture. As you wander through its labyrinthine alleys, you will discover hidden squares, magnificent churches like the Barcelona Cathedral, and remnants of the Roman era. The Gothic Quarter is also home to charming cafes, boutique shops, and vibrant street performers, making it a perfect place to experience the rich history and lively culture of Barcelona.</string>
    <string name="c2l6">A bustling hub of activity, La Boqueria Market is a must-visit in Barcelona. Located along the famous La Rambla, this vibrant market is a feast for the senses, offering a dazzling array of fresh produce, seafood, meats, and local delicacies. Strolling through its colorful stalls, visitors can taste traditional Catalan treats, discover exotic fruits, and experience the lively atmosphere that captures the essence of Barcelona. La Boqueria Market is not just a place to shop, but a cultural experience that brings the flavors and spirit of the city to life.</string>

    <string name="c3l1">A vibrant and iconic landmark, Shibuya Crossing in Tokyo is one of the busiest pedestrian intersections in the world. Located in the heart of the Shibuya district, this bustling crossroads is a symbol of Tokyos dynamic urban energy. As the traffic lights turn red, waves of people from all directions converge in a mesmerizing display of organized chaos. Surrounded by towering buildings adorned with bright advertisements and giant screens, Shibuya Crossing offers an unforgettable experience both day and night. It is also a shoppers paradise, with trendy boutiques and massive department stores like Shibuya 109 offering the latest fashions. Whether youre people-watching from a nearby café, shopping for the newest trends, or joining the throngs to cross, Shibuya Crossing encapsulates the fast-paced spirit of Tokyo!</string>
    <string name="c3l2">A marvel of modern engineering, Tokyo Skytree is one of the tallest structures in the world, standing at 634 meters. Located in the Sumida City Ward, it offers breathtaking panoramic views of Tokyo and beyond. Visitors can ascend to the observation decks for stunning vistas, especially beautiful at sunset and night when the city is illuminated. The Skytree also features a shopping complex, an aquarium, and numerous dining options, making it a hub of entertainment and culture. Whether marveling at the view or exploring its attractions, Tokyo Skytree is an unforgettable experience in the heart of Tokyo!</string>
    <string name="c3l3">A beloved family destination, Ueno Zoo is Japans oldest zoo, located in Ueno Park, Tokyo. Established in 1882, the zoo is home to over 3,000 animals from 400 species, including giant pandas, tigers, and elephants. Visitors can explore various themed areas, such as the Gorilla and Tiger Forest and the Japanese Animals section. The zoo also features a five-story pagoda and a charming monorail that connects the eastern and western sections. With its rich history and diverse wildlife, Ueno Zoo offers an engaging and educational experience for visitors of all ages!</string>
    <string name="c3l4">A historic and spiritual landmark, Senso-ji is Tokyos oldest temple, located in the Asakusa district. Founded in 645 AD, it is dedicated to Kannon, the Buddhist goddess of mercy. The temples iconic Thunder Gate (Kaminarimon) and its giant red lantern welcome millions of visitors each year. Stroll through the bustling Nakamise shopping street, leading up to the temple, where traditional snacks and souvenirs are sold. The main hall and the five-story pagoda offer a glimpse into Japans rich cultural heritage. Senso-ji is not just a place of worship, but a vibrant symbol of Tokyos history and tradition!</string>
    <string name="c3l5">A treasure trove of Japanese art and culture, the Tokyo National Museum is the oldest and largest museum in Japan. Located in Ueno Park, it showcases an extensive collection of over 110,000 artifacts, including samurai armor, ancient ceramics, and traditional paintings. The museums stunning architecture blends traditional and modern styles, enhancing the overall experience. Visitors can explore various exhibitions that highlight the rich history and cultural heritage of Japan, from ancient times to the present. With its vast collections and beautiful gardens, the Tokyo National Museum is a must-visit for anyone interested in Japans artistic legacy</string>
    <string name="c3l6">A stunning blend of history and tranquility, the Tokyo Imperial Palace serves as the primary residence of the Emperor of Japan. Nestled in the heart of Tokyo, the palace is surrounded by beautifully landscaped gardens, historic moats, and ancient stone walls. While the inner grounds are not open to the public, visitors can explore the East Gardens, which offer a glimpse into the palaces rich history and stunning scenery. The iconic Nijubashi Bridge provides a picturesque view of the palace, especially during cherry blossom season. With its serene atmosphere and historical significance, the Tokyo Imperial Palace is a peaceful retreat amid the bustling city!</string>
    <string name="c3l7">A breathtaking symbol of Japan, Mount Fuji is the Japans tallest peak, standing at 3,776 meters. This iconic stratovolcano is located on Honshu Island and is often adorned with snow at its summit, creating a stunning contrast against the clear blue sky. Mount Fuji is surrounded by beautiful landscapes, including lakes and cherry blossom trees, making it a popular destination for photographers and nature lovers. Hikers can enjoy various trails leading to the summit, while those preferring a more leisurely experience can admire the mountain from nearby parks and viewpoints. With its majestic beauty and cultural significance, Mount Fuji is a must-see for anyone visiting Japan!</string>
    <string name="c3l8">A magical destination for families and Disney enthusiasts, Tokyo Disney Resort features two enchanting theme parks: Tokyo Disneyland and Tokyo DisneySea. Visitors can experience thrilling rides, captivating shows, and meet beloved Disney characters in beautifully themed environments. With its unique blend of Japanese culture and Disney charm, the resort offers an unforgettable adventure for guests of all ages. From enchanting parades to exquisite dining options, Tokyo Disney Resort is a dream come true for anyone looking to experience the magic of Disney in a truly unique setting.</string>

    <string name="c4l1">A stunning architectural marvel in Dubai, Burj Khalifa stands as the tallest building in the world, reaching an impressive height of 828 meters. Visitors can take an exhilarating elevator ride to the observation deck on the 148th floor for breathtaking panoramic views of the city skyline and the surrounding desert. The towers sleek design, adorned with intricate patterns and illuminated by thousands of LED lights at night, captivates everyone who sees it. The Burj Khalifa also houses luxury apartments, corporate suites, and the renowned Atmosphere restaurant, making it a must-visit destination for anyone exploring Dubai.</string>
    <string name="c4l2">A thrilling water paradise in Dubai, Atlantis Aquaventure Waterpark offers an exhilarating experience for all ages. With a range of exciting water slides, lazy rivers, and pristine beaches, visitors can enjoy endless fun under the sun. The park features unique attractions like the Aquaconda, the worlds largest water slide, and the Shark Lagoon, where guests can get up close with marine life. With its luxurious surroundings and top-notch amenities, Atlantis Aquaventure promises an unforgettable day of adventure and relaxation for families and thrill-seekers alike.</string>
    <string name="c4l3">A premier shopping and entertainment destination, Dubai Mall is one of the largest malls in the world. It boasts over 1,200 retail outlets, ranging from luxury brands to popular high-street shops, ensuring a shopping experience like no other. Visitors can enjoy a variety of attractions, including an impressive indoor aquarium, an ice rink, and a virtual reality park. With an array of dining options, from casual eateries to fine dining, Dubai Mall offers something for everyone. Its proximity to the iconic Burj Khalifa and the mesmerizing Dubai Fountain adds to the allure, making it a must-visit hub of culture and entertainment in the heart of the city.</string>
    <string name="c4l4">An iconic symbol of luxury in Dubai, Burj Al Arab is renowned for its distinctive sail-shaped silhouette and opulent interiors. Standing on its own artificial island, this five-star hotel offers unparalleled views of the Arabian Gulf and a wealth of lavish amenities. Guests can indulge in world-class dining experiences, including the renowned Al Muntaha restaurant, perched high above the city. With its stunning architecture and exceptional service, Burj Al Arab epitomizes the extravagant lifestyle that Dubai is known for, making it a must-see landmark for travelers seeking a taste of ultimate luxury.</string>
    <string name="c4l5">A mesmerizing underwater experience located within the Dubai Mall, the Dubai Aquarium is one of the largest suspended aquariums in the world. Home to over 33,000 marine animals, including sharks, rays, and colorful fish, it offers visitors an up-close view of fascinating aquatic life. Guests can explore the 48-meter-long tunnel that provides a 270-degree view of the aquarium, making it feel like walking through an underwater world. The aquarium also features interactive experiences such as shark diving and glass-bottom boat tours, providing an unforgettable adventure for families and marine enthusiasts alike.</string>
    <string name="c4l6">A stunning floral paradise, Dubai Miracle Garden is the world’s largest natural flower garden, featuring over 150 million blooms in breathtaking designs and sculptures. Visitors can wander through vibrant displays, including heart-shaped arches, towering structures, and whimsical themes that change seasonally. The garden is not only a visual delight but also offers a peaceful retreat from the bustling city, inviting guests to relax amidst natures beauty. With its innovative landscape and enchanting atmosphere, Dubai Miracle Garden is a must-visit destination for flower lovers and those seeking a unique outdoor experience.</string>

    <string name="c5l1">A quintessential symbol of New York City, the Empire State Building stands tall at 1,454 feet, offering panoramic views from its observation decks on the 86th and 102nd floors. Completed in 1931, this Art Deco skyscraper is a marvel of engineering and design, attracting millions of visitors each year. The buildings iconic spire, illuminated in various colors to mark special occasions, adds to its grandeur. Visitors can explore exhibits on the buildings history and significance, enjoying the stunning vistas that make the Empire State Building a must-see attraction in the heart of Manhattan.</string>
    <string name="c5l2">An enduring symbol of freedom and democracy, the Statue of Liberty stands proudly on Liberty Island in New York Harbor. Gifted by France in 1886, this iconic monument welcomes visitors with its towering presence and rich history. Standing at 305 feet, Lady Liberty offers breathtaking views from her pedestal and crown. The statues museum provides an insightful look into its construction, symbolism, and significance. A visit to the Statue of Liberty is a profound experience, celebrating the ideals of liberty and hope that define the American spirit.</string>
    <string name="c5l3">A vibrant and bustling hub, Times Square is the heart of New York Citys entertainment district. Known for its bright, neon lights and towering digital billboards, it offers a sensory overload of sights and sounds. Visitors can experience the electric atmosphere, with a multitude of theaters, shops, and restaurants lining the streets. Times Square is also famous for its New Years Eve celebration, where the iconic ball drop draws crowds from around the world. Whether its catching a Broadway show or simply soaking in the lively ambiance, Times Square is a must-visit destination that embodies the energy and excitement of the city.</string>
    <string name="c5l4">A serene oasis in the midst of New York Citys urban hustle, Central Park spans 843 acres, offering a tranquil escape for both locals and visitors. With its expansive lawns, wooded areas, and picturesque water bodies, the park provides a diverse landscape for recreation and relaxation. Visitors can enjoy leisurely walks, bike rides, picnics, and seasonal activities such as ice skating in the winter. Central Parks iconic landmarks, including Bethesda Terrace, Bow Bridge, and the Central Park Zoo, enhance its charm. This green haven is a testament to natures beauty and a beloved retreat in the heart of Manhattan.</string>
    <string name="c5l5">A cultural treasure in New York City, the Metropolitan Museum of Art, often called the Met, houses one of the worlds most extensive and diverse art collections. Spanning over 5,000 years of history, its galleries feature masterpieces from ancient civilizations, European paintings, modern art, and more. Visitors can explore exhibits ranging from Egyptian artifacts to Renaissance sculptures and contemporary works. The Mets grand architecture and renowned exhibitions make it a must-visit destination for art enthusiasts and anyone seeking to immerse themselves in the rich tapestry of human creativity and expression.</string>
    <string name="c5l6">Paris is the centre of a national, and with air travel, international, complex transport system. The modern system has been superimposed on a complex map of streets and wide boulevards that were set in their current routes in the 19th century. On a national level, it is the centre of a web of road and railway, and at a more local level, it is covered with a dense mesh of bus, tram and metro service networks.</string>






</resources>